you still haven't handed those over that's because the 14th was on a Sunday and it's not like this is
anything great but she gave me some chocolate on Valentine's Day so I got some cookies from like a
random corner store or whatever or whatever quit trying to play it down like that look at that
perfect wrapping paper you use it's not like that besides my sights are still only set on hooking up
with Yamada this is just a little token of gratitude for Sekine gratitude for what you only got what
everyone else did in class lies mine had a cute heart in it which goes to show it was special
so what's your plan well the plan is go casually toss these cookies in her shoe box and since you'll
just happen to see it you're gonna tell Sekine Arachi did that he put him in Arachi like that like hell
whatever it's still the plan here goes this is ridiculous okay Sekine's boxes
what's that crap I threw it in Yamada's not Sekine's look there's a letter on the back
no wait it's not you see see what oh I get it now don't mind me I'm just gonna head on home
wait no listen it's just stop let me go yeah yeah enough you're gonna go in there and say thank you
I am not letting my cookies go to waste it's Arachi's mom go on
what's up so um that chocolate was really delicious and it was all thoughtfully handmade
and I really liked it and that was really nice you know did you forget the part where everyone in
class got some yeah but there you go later yeah she smelled really nice don't you think huh oh yeah
here shoot I didn't get a chance to tell her those aren't from me let's see what it says
dear lover chocolate was totes amazing super thanks hope we can keep being lovey-dovey kiss kiss kiss
hard킹-lim2-3-3
lovejapx mul5-u1
lovejapx
Today, we say farewell to this classroom.
It's the last time we'll all be together here.
Hey, the school likes to split up groups of friends when we change classes, don't they?
Yeah, that's what I've heard.
Well, I've got a plan brewing in my head.
Idiots! Morons!
I've always hated the both of you!
You're so stupid!
Wait, what's going on?
Teacher!
I was never friends or anything with these dumb, overgrown, vapid idiots!
I'm glad I'm getting split from them next year!
And Yamada!
Hey, Yamada, remember we talked about this?
Anyway, teacher, please keep me out of the same class as these brainless fools!
Oh, you don't say. Okay then.
What?
Wait, that's not... by Yashiko!
We live in the tiniest of bubbles.
Ichikawa, give me your line ID!
Me too!
And me!
A tiny bubble we call the classroom.
We aren't allowed to play in here.
No one's got enough!
Ugh!
I kinda just wanted to stick around.
Guess you wanted to hang out longer too, I take it.
Me?
Not really.
Okay.
Let's play a little one-on-one.
Seriously?
Whoever loses has to do whatever the winner wishes no matter what.
That's not fair!
Ugh!
Knocked cash!
Oh!
Ugh!
Not really...
Okay...
Let's play a little one-on-one.
Seriously?
Whoever loses has to do whatever the winner wishes no matter what.
You're not much of a shot.
Whatever!
I'm a whole lot better on defense.
If I get this in...
Sorry!
If I get this in, I'm gonna...
Ask her out!
No such luck.
What?
That was my basket!
Too bad!
That means you lost the ball!
I put it in, so I win!
Let's just say that didn't count then.
You really like basketball, huh?
It's only because you're playing with me.
Now with that out of the way, what should I ask for?
Can I...
Can...
Do you think...
I can call you Kyo?
Huh?
What?
Yeah, I mean, of coo-
Hey!
Hurry up and get on home!
Kyo!
So what do you think, Kyo?
Kyo?
Hey!
Hi, Kyo!
Oh, Kyo!
Kyo!
Go on and call her Ana, then!
Sigh...
Who...
Who are you?
Lucifer Nigorikoa.
Your natural instinct.
Your libido.
What?
I am what grows massive when your feelings
get you all turned on.
Hey, little bro.
What?
Don't burst in here without knocking.
Mom says she's going to make sukiyaki for your birthday
the day after tomorrow.
It's going to be a party.
We never have a party for my birthday.
What are you talking about?
Oh, come on.
This year isn't like all the rest.
You're a popular boy now.
Are you going out somewhere instead?
No.
Yamada's busy with work over break
and I also have cram school.
What?
When did I even mention little Ana celebrating with us, huh?
Oh, shut up.
Get out of my room.
A whole lot of nothing happened,
and my birthday was here.
Same as always, really.
It's a special day.
Maybe I can...
You always walk home alone like this?
Yeah.
Except when it's really late, then I get someone.
That seems pretty dangerous.
For you too, Ichikawa.
You walk home alone, right?
Yeah, but that's me.
Hmm?
Ichikawa.
Do you think I can call you Kyo?
Did I mishear her or something?
I don't know.
It's true.
To you too.
I don't know.
For you too, Ichikawa.
Did she think you're leaving early, it's just too bad?
But that's me.
Ugh?
Hm?
Ichikawa?
Do you think I can call you Kyo?
Did I mishear her or something?
Or does she think me leaving early
usually meant that I don't want her to?
Maybe I should...
Sure thing.
Call me Kyo.
Not happening!
That would be so weird!
Hm?
What's going on?
I feel like I'm being watched.
Is someone following us?
They're getting close.
No way.
What do I do?
What?
Huh?
I gotta protect her with my life!
Keep her safe!
Hey there.
It is you.
Jeez, Dad.
You scared me!
Sorry.
Wasn't sure you'd want me to butt in.
Huh?
Oh, uh, good evening, sir!
Sorry for spooking you.
I was just out picking up the cake we ordered.
You have cake?
Are you celebrating something?
Yeah, it's his birthday.
Huh?
Yeah.
Wait, what?
It's today?
Why didn't you say anything?
We're having Matsusaka beef sukiyaki.
Huh?
You wanna...
come over?
Uh...
Uh-huh!
What?
This is gonna be a celebration!
Yeah, so I won't need dinner.
That's fine.
But whose house?
Oh, um, I'm at, uh...
Hey, Ana!
Huh?
Oh, a girl?
What?
Uh-huh.
Yeah, Kana.
Is that so?
I gotta go now!
Why did you go and change your clothes?
Oh, this is just party wear.
You look cute!
Come on now, smile!
Quit torturing me.
Um, happy birthday, Q.
Wait, what?
Oh, right!
Sorry about that.
Have some.
Eat as much as you would like.
Oh, no, please.
Don't worry.
I don't need much.
I, uh, I'm actually a really light eater.
The biggest lie there ever was.
That explains why you're so skinny.
I'm almost worried for you.
Yeah, you look like a model.
Yeah, I am.
What?
So, wait, you're really a model?
In amateur magazines?
Oh, no, in professional ones.
I even have a talent agency and everything.
Yes, she's a pro model.
Pro?
Uh-uh.
Seriously, what was I thinking dressing like this?
I know that feeling.
Kana, there's still more beer.
Oh, let me get that for you.
Oh.
Uh, a drink from a real model.
Chill out.
Oh, how about you, sir?
I'm drinking tea.
Mm-hmm.
Kana, didn't you go get a present for your brother?
What?
Uh, that can wait for later.
Just hand it over, sis.
Oh, okay.
It's a bunny figure of that game character you said you like.
You can't be serious!
Why are all these girly figures in bunny outfits?
They aren't.
This figure just happens to be the bunny outfit version.
Uh-huh.
Dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun-dun.
That's wedding music you're singing.
Oh, you're right.
Well, um...
Happy birthday to you.
Happy birthday, dear Kyokyo.
Okay, little bro.
Now make a wish.
I hope I stay healthy.
Nice, Grandpa.
Happy birthday to you, Kyokyo.
Kyokyo?
Hmm?
There's been a murder!
You can't just do that at a time like this!
What do you think of this, Anna?
You look cute!
Really?
Even in your model eyes?
Very, very adorable!
Hang on.
You're gonna say that about everything, aren't you?
Are they besties already?
It's almost 9.30, Yamada.
Will your parents worry?
Maybe I should get going.
What?
You spend the night here!
Momo and Hinako stayed over the other night, so it's fine!
Tell them, Mom!
Well, so long as she's fine with it.
You see?
Uh-oh, if I won't be a bother.
This is bad.
Real bad!
Yeah, do you mind?
Are their parents okay with this?
Hello!
This is Ichikawa's mother speaking.
Sorry to trouble you so late at night.
I'm sorry, Ichikawa?
Our daughters just seem to be getting along so well.
Yamada's gonna spend the night.
But wait.
My parents and my sister are still here.
There's nothing bad about this.
I'm gonna let Yamada use the bath first, all right?
The bath?!
Come on, relax!
You're not going to be in there together!
This is no different than when Kana's friends stay over.
Yamada and Kana are just gonna stay up all night together.
Here you go.
These sweats are for her pajamas.
I didn't have any brand new ones.
Oh, also, the panties you're holding are some.
I've only one one.
Grow up and quit acting like you just picked up a cockroach.
I think you can handle the rest, okay?
Yeah.
What?
Hey!
No!
She passed out?
Uh...
Um...
I've brought clothes.
Uh, okay.
These underwear...
They're, um, my sisters.
You don't have to wear them.
You can use the washing machine if you want to wear your own.
Kay.
I'll leave now.
Hey!
Hmm?
Do you have a rubber?
Ugh!
Oh, sorry.
I forgot mine.
Did I maybe leave it on the sink?
The sink?
Oh, a rubber band!
Um, I'll leave it here.
Somebody help!
Sorry, it's so cramped.
No, thank you.
For the clothes to...
I couldn't just not take a bath.
But I didn't use her bath water.
And catching sight of my sister's underwear was enough to cool my head.
Water.
I'm only here for some water.
Oh, Amazaki!
Yeah, well, you only ate, like, two bites of dinner.
Me?
You sure were paying attention.
I just...
That a script?
Yeah.
We film in two days.
Weren't you a little too busy to hang out then?
No, I was just reading it because I couldn't get to sleep.
Oh, my God.
Is it for a movie?
Yeah.
It's about a girl in her rebellious stage who lashes out at her parents.
But it's so hard.
Everything will be ruined if I don't get it right, you know?
Um, must be nerve-wracking.
What a lame comment.
It's just, I've never had a rebellious face.
That must be nice for you.
What?
Have you, Ichikawa?
Isn't it obvious?
But how come?
You have such nice parents.
How should I know?
But it's not like I'm mad at them.
I'm mad at not letting myself be me.
Worried that maybe I'm not such a good kid.
What am I even saying?
That probably doesn't really help you at all, but...
Huh?
What is this feeling?
My heart is racing, but I feel so at ease.
There's something so strange about her.
Thank you.
I'm excited to play the part now.
Then, Kana joined a band because she wanted to be popular.
I'm so excited.
I feel so.
I'm like, how are you going?
cles orgallous comment onaring me.
I know I'm about to play speed.
You Golf Bin.
I know he's been talking to me now.
Well, they seem to be bad for me.
I do not know.
Is it better?
No.
Good night.
Wait a minute, Kana's underwear went unused, and the washing machine was running!
Yamada's not wearing-